What are you doing?
你在幹嘛？
I feel like
you don't believe me.
我覺得你不相信我
It's starting to drive me crazy.
我覺得快要瘋了
It's not fair that
you don't believe me.
這樣不公平
我什麼時候騙過你了？
When have I ever lied to you?
I believe you.
我相信你
Obviously, you don't. Or you
wouldn't be acting like this.
你顯然不相信
不然就不會有這種表現了
And it's...
It's fucked up. We've always
been honest with each other.
這太糟了
我們一直都對彼此很坦誠
所以放過我吧
So, just... give me a break.
- No, we haven't.
- We haven't?
－我們沒有對彼此坦誠
－沒有嗎？
I mean,
we're not honest about...
我們沒有誠實說出‥
About what?
說出什麼？
About how we're not
attracted to each other...
我們對彼此已經沒有吸引力了
anymore.
Or at least you're not attracted
to me, you know?
或者說我對你沒有吸引力
It's, like, I get it you're on
top of the world right now.
我能理解，你現在是大人物了
You could sleep with...
想跟誰上床都可以‥
whoever you want,
－卻被我困住了‥
－別說這種話
- and you're stuck with me and...
- Stop saying that stuff!
Yeah, it makes sense that
你想跟意大利妓女
上床也是正常的
you'd wanna have sex
with an Italian hooker.
- You're not getting any.
- I didn't have sex
－你沒有得到滿足
－我沒跟意大利妓女上床，夠了
with an Italian hooker.
Jesus, fuck!
I'm just saying
that it's not the cheating
我想說的是
我在意的不是你出軌
- that bothers me so much...
- There was no cheating!
我沒有出軌‥
There was no cheating!
我在意的是我們之間的問題
As what it says about us.
我們之間什麼問題？
What?
What does it say?
That maybe something has died.
或許有些情感已經消失了
We are too young
to be this old, Ethan.
我不希望我們在這個年齡
就陷入死胡同，伊森
I'm sure you don't want that
part of your life to be over.
你也不想就此告別那樣的人生吧？
Do you?
我就不想
I don't.
I'm dealing with a lot, okay?
我很多事要煩惱，好嗎？
工作負擔大得要命‥
Work's been insane. And...
Okay.
好
- I don't know.
- I... I...
我也不知道‥
We can work on it.
我們會想辦法‥好不好？
We can work on it, okay?
Do even want me?
你想要我嗎？
我愛你
I love you.
太令人憂鬱了
- So depressing.
- "I love you" is depressing?
＂我愛你＂讓你覺得憂鬱？
不是‥
No. No.
I love you, too.
我也愛你
Are you gonna go running
or what?
你要去慢跑嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道
- You want a coffee?
- Yes, please.
－你要咖啡嗎？
－好，謝謝
她覺得你們趁我們在諾托
做了不該做的事
You know, she's pretty convinced
you guys did something bad
- when we were in Noto.
- Ooh, something bad?
不該做的事？
- Mm.
- Like what?
－像是什麼？
－我不知道
I don't know.
- What'd you do this time?
- I told you. We partied.
你這次做了什麼？
我說過了，開派對狂歡
- How hard did you party?
- So hard, honey.
你玩多瘋？
－太瘋了，老婆
－是嗎？
- Yeah?
- So...
太瘋了
fucking hard!
- Because you left me.
- Oh.
因為你丟下我
- Yeah. You abandoned me.
- Yeah?
－你拋棄了我
－是嗎？
現在你得付出代價
And now, you must pay.
What about you?
那你呢？
You fuck anyone in Noto?
你在諾托有沒有和人上床？
Any fat Italian guys
with BO and a dirty dick?
老二髒髒的意大利臭胖子？
- Every single one.
- You little...
每一個都上了
你這女人‥
Oh, yeah.
- Oh, you're gonna pay.
- Mm.
你完蛋了
歌劇好看嗎？
- So, how was the opera?
- Mm.
- She died.
- Who?
－她死了
－誰啊？
- Madame Butterfly.
- Oh.
蝴蝶夫人
那你昨晚過得如何？
How was your big night?
很好玩
It was fun.
Yeah. We almost got arrested.
對
我們差點就被逮捕了
We didn't pay
for our arancini. So,
我們沒付炸燉飯球的錢
- yeah.
- Arancinis cost a dollar.
－炸燉飯球只要一美元
－我知道
I know.
Maybe you should
slow down with this guy.
也許你不該陷得太深
為什麼？
Why?
Something about his relationship
with his uncle.
他和叔叔的關係有點怪
怎麼說？
What about it?
- I don't think it's his uncle.
- It is.
我覺得他們不是叔姪關係
是啦
Mm-mm.
Why would you say that?
你為什麼這麼說？
我只是‥
Oh, it was just a...
有種強烈的直覺
It was just a strong hunch.
好喔
Okay?
波蒂亞
Portia.
When I see you, I... I see
a younger version of me.
我覺得你就像年輕時的我
You know,
when I was a little girl,
小時候
my mother used to dress
me up like a little doll.
我媽媽喜歡把我
打扮得漂漂亮亮的
And I was always a little doll,
我就像洋娃娃
永遠等著別人來跟我玩
waiting for someone
to play with me.
You know,
when you're empty inside
如果你內心空虛，人生缺乏方向
and you have no direction,
you'll end up
in some crazy places, right?
就會遇到許多瘋狂的事情
But you'll still be lost.
但你還是會覺得很迷惘
What are you
trying to say? Like...
你想說什麼？
Get your shit together, Portia.
振作一點，波蒂亞
Buongiorno, ladies.
兩位早安
Pineapple mimosa?
要來杯鳳梨含羞草嗎？
－好
－當然
- Mm. Yes.
- Oh, sure.
－你們睡得好嗎？
－不太好
- How did we sleep?
- Not great.
There were some
strange noises in the night.
夜裡傳來一些奇怪的噪音
Oh, no.
不好了
Well, we need you refreshed,
you're guest of honor tonight.
那你得好好休息
你可是今晚的貴賓
Oh.
Today's the big day!
今天是大日子，我們要拜訪故土
Gonna visit the motherland.
Wouldn't it be cool
如果能找到血親，那就太酷了
if we actually found
some blood relations?
You know, uh, Marty Fiorina,
馬蒂費歐里納也在普利亞尋根過
he did something like this,
but in Puglia.
結果找到一整個大家庭
Found his entire
extended family.
一起吃豐盛午餐，喝葡萄酒，拍照
They had a big lunch,
they drank wine,
they took photos.
Oh. A real homecoming.
貨真價實的尋根之旅
那樣就太好了
- That would be nice.
- I found us a translator.
－我找到了一個翻譯
－好主意
Good thinking.
這週的謎題，然後我又得回樓上
Sì.
後來我們去游泳，吃飯
一起喝杯好咖啡
（意語）早安
Buongiorno!
Buongiorno.
有我的信嗎？
我叫露西亞格列柯
應該沒有
就我所知沒有
Salvatore? Salvatore!
沙爾瓦多
有沒有露西亞格列柯的信？
沒有，抱歉
該死的王八蛋
你滿意我昨晚的表現嗎？
我唱得很好吧？
抱歉，我現在沒時間
請你們離開吧
Hey!
- What are you trying to do?
- What do you mean?
－你們想怎樣？
－什麼意思？
你們不打算付錢嗎？
Are you trying not to pay us?
- Were you not paid?
- You owe us 1,300 Euros.
－你們沒拿到錢嗎？
－你們還欠一千三百歐元
I'll get it sorted,
we have money.
我會處理，我們有錢‥
I... I didn't realize you
hadn't been paid, okay?
我不知道你們沒拿到錢
Yes.
對
- Ciao.
（意語）你好‥
Salvatore?
沙爾瓦多
抱歉，麻煩去站大櫃臺
那裡現在沒人
喬萬尼在那裡
那就去看母豬生小豬了沒有
－去啊　－好
今天是我生日
－生日快樂，我都不知道　－謝謝
Grazie.
我在想‥
如果你剛好有空‥
下班之後‥
可以一起去喝一杯
慶祝一下？
如果你有事也沒關係
我沒事，我們去喝酒吧
- Ah, sì?
- Sì
－（意語）真的嗎？
－（意語）真的
太好了
生日快樂
Grazie!
－恭喜你
－謝謝
你在這裡做什麼？
你看，外面有客人需要幫忙
Hey.
What?
又怎麼了？
I just saw you
talking to those hookers.
我剛才看到你跟那兩個妓女說話
I'm so hungover.
我宿醉很嚴重
今天只能躺在沙灘上
I think the only thing I can do
today is lay on the beach.
Detox.
- Please stop gaslighting me.
- I'm not gaslighting you.
別耍我
我沒有耍你
Look, I can explain,
聽著，我能解釋
但能不能不要現在談？
just can we please
not talk about it right now?
Okay, whatever.
隨便你
I'm over it. I don't...
I don't care anymore.
算了，我已經不在乎了
Just looking at all those
sausages made me wanna puke.
看到一堆香腸就好想吐
Oh!
Oh, my God!
天啊
- Sorry.
- Shit!
－抱歉
－真是的
Scared the widdle baby, did I?
嚇哭了吧？
沒事啦
Right.
I got the car for the day.
Do you wanna take a drive?
我今天能用車，想去兜風嗎？
We'll go down to Cefalù,
we'll drink some Peronis,
我們可以去切法盧喝啤酒
eat some ice cream.
What do you think?
吃冰淇淋，你覺得如何？
- Sure, yeah!
- Yeah?
－當然
－可以嗎？
I'm down for anything.
去哪裡都行
但我想回來參加派對
I just wanna be back
for the party thing later.
好‥
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- We'll be back. Don't worry.
- Okay.
－我們會趕回來，別擔心
－好
Uh, go grab all your shit,
meet me by the car, all right?
去拿你的東西
我們在車子那裡碰頭，好嗎？
我帶了叔叔的信用卡‥
Got me uncle's credit card, so,
you know.
你走吧‥
- All right. Go.
- Oh, fuck!
－可惡，夠了喔
－抱歉‥
- Oh my God!
- Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry,
- I was just teasing.
- So mean!
你好壞
Shit!
真是的
Is that...
那是我的帽子嗎？
Wouldn't it be incredible
要是能找到遠親就太棒了
if we actually found
some distant relatives?
Would be amazing.
你說得沒錯
Just try not to fall before
we get you in the car, Dad.
爸，上車前別跌倒了
- Oh. Thanks a lot, Dom!
- Hey, guys.
－多謝提醒
－來了
This is Lucia.
She's going to translate for us.
這是露西亞，她是我們的翻譯
This is my dad, Dominic,
and my grandfather, Bert.
這是我爸爸多米尼克
和我爺爺伯特
幸會，早安
My pleasure. Good morning!
你好‥
- Hi.
- I've seen you around.
- Ah, yes! I am always around.
我看過你
對，我常來這裡
- I love this hotel, so...
- Hey, Lucia?
－我很愛這間飯店‥
－露西亞
Oh! Just... just one second.
等一下
Sorry, Albie,
I thought you meant, um,
抱歉，阿爾比
我以為你找的是飯店員工
someone who worked here
in the hotel.
有問題嗎？
Is there a problem?
Oh, I... I don't know
if this is a good idea.
我不確定這樣好不好
Dad, she's coming, okay?
So, be polite.
爸，她會跟我們去
禮貌一點
You're overreacting.
你反應太大了
- Giving yourself away.
- What? Giving what away?
－會漏餡的
－漏什麼餡？
－你睡過她
－夠了，我不希望她來
That you slept with her.
Stop it, please.
I don't want her to come.
你是怎麼了？
What's wrong with you?
Can't you just be cool?
不能隨和一點嗎？
Get it together.
振作起來
Okay, guys. What...
Uh, let's... let's do this.
你們，要出發了
You seem to know
a lot of the staff here.
你感覺跟這裡的員工很熟
Uh. Yes. Uh, he is the brother
of a friend of mine.
對，他是我朋友的哥哥
- Ah!
- Thank you.
So, tell us about yourself,
my dear. Where are you from?
聊聊你自己吧，親愛的
你是哪裡人？
卡塔尼亞本地人
I'm from Catania.
Ah. How do you speak
such good English?
－你的英語怎麼這麼好？
－在學校學的
From school.
And... from my work.
還有工作中學到的
Oh, what do you?
你從事哪一行？
觀光服務業
Hospitality.
High unemployment rate
in Sicily, I hear, so it's...
我聽說西西里的失業率很高
你有工作，這是好事
It's great that you're employed!
謝謝，我確實很幸運
Thank you, yes. I'm lucky.
I really wanna get a massage
before we go home.
回家前我想去按摩
你今天想去按摩嗎？
Do you wanna get massages today?
Yeah, sure.
好啊，當然
好，那我打去問他們有沒有時間
'Kay, I'm gonna call and see
if they have any availability.
Want me
to get you another towel?
老兄
Dude!
Can we sit here?
這裡可以坐嗎？
- You are fucking me up here!
- What? How?
－我被你整慘了
－怎麼說？
Harper is, like, 100 percent
convinced I cheated on her.
哈珀覺得我一定背著她偷吃
－但你沒有啊
－這我知道
- But you didn't, man.
- I know that!
But, could you at least,
like, I dunno,
但你至少可以幫我說句話吧？
vouch for me or something?
Hi! I was wondering,
你好
我想請問今天
能預約兩位按摩嗎？
do you have room for two
for a massage today?
Oh. Okay.
這樣啊
Yeah. Daphne Sullivan.
對，達芙妮蘇利文
１０９號房
109.
Thanks.
謝謝
Okay.
我約到最後一個空位
但現在就得過去
I got the last massage,
but it's, like, right now.
- Are you sure you don't want it?
- No, you take it.
你確定不想按嗎？
你去吧
You're the one going home
to a house full of kids.
你回家還得照顧孩子
Um. Okay, I'm gonna go,
那我過去了
'cause I wanna use
the steam room.
－我想用蒸氣室
－好，去吧
Yeah. Yeah, totally.
So... but
I'll see you in a few hours?
－幾個小時後見
－慢慢來
- Take your time.
- Bye.
再見
E, you wanna go
get some drinks, man?
伊森，你想去喝東西嗎？
不用了
No, I'm good.
- I'll go.
- Yeah?
－我跟你去
－你要喝？
對，走吧
Yeah. Let's do it.
Hmm.
Do you have any goals?
你有什麼目標嗎？
What?
什麼？
－目標？
－對啊
- Goals?
- Yeah.
- What are some of your goals?
- I don't know.
－那你的目標是什麼？
－我也不知道
Be satisfied?
滿足嗎？
Yeah, that'd be nice.
要是能滿足就太好了
I think you just gotta live
every day as it comes,
我覺得要過一天算一天
do you know what I mean?
至少我是這樣啦
Like, that's what I'd do anyway.
Who knows if we're even
gonna be here tomorrow?
誰知道我們能不能活到明天？
也是啦
Yeah.
That's very true.
The world's a fucked-up place.
你說得很對，這個世界很糟糕
So...
What's wrong with it?
哪裡糟糕了？
Are you joking?
你在說笑嗎？
Pretty fucking good world,
I'd say.
我覺得這個世界很棒啊
Literally everything's
falling apart.
一切都要分崩離析了
You'd rather live in
the Middle Ages then, would ya?
那你寧願活在中世紀嗎？
When they were ripping
each other to shreds, yeah?
以前自相殘殺是家常便飯
They were way worse
than ISIS or any of them lot.
當時的人比伊斯蘭國那些人殘忍多了
Like, it's a fucking miracle
anyone's even left in Europe.
歐洲還有人能活下來
根本就是奇蹟
All we've been doing is just
我們只會把彼此切成碎肉
fuckin' hacking
each other to bits
and burning
each other at the stake.
或是綁在木樁上燒死
I'm ready for another beer.
我要再來一瓶啤酒
All I'm saying is, right,
我的意思是，我們很幸運了
we're fucking lucky,
do you know what I mean?
Like, we're living in the...
能生活在歷史上最好的時代
best time
in the history of the world,
on the best fucking planet.
生在最棒的星球上
If you can't be satisfied
living now, here...
如果生在此時此地都還不知足
you're never gonna be satisfied.
你永遠不會滿足
So, let's get pissed, eh?
我們去喝個爛醉吧
走吧
- Come on.
- My...
－等等‥
－趕快拿
- I'll grab that.
- Wait! Wait!
＂特斯塔德阿瓜＂
這裡沒什麼東西
Not much to it.
- Hmm.
- No wonder they all left.
難怪他們都離開了
Who would I have been
if I lived here?
要是我住這裡
會變成什麼樣子？
You wouldn't have lived here,
you would've left.
你不會待在這裡，你一定會離開的
There are people who stay
and there are people who leave.
有些人會留下，有些人會離開
- And I'm someone who leaves?
- Hmm,
我屬於會離開的人？
你會渴望到處流浪
是我傳給你的
'cause you got wanderlust.
You get that from me.
All righty.
Okay. All right, um,
you're not gonna believe this.
好
你們一定不相信
我們跟那個女人談過
We just talked
to that woman and she said
她說狄格拉索家還有人住在這裡
that there is a Di Grasso family
still living here
and she knows them.
而且她認識
- You're kidding!
- Amazing!
－不會吧
－太棒了
They live a mile down the road,
and she gave us the address.
他們住在一英里外
她給了我地址
- Let's go!
- Oh!
走吧
- What's wrong?
- Alessio.
－怎麼了？
－是艾勒修
- He followed us here?
- Albie, come on.
－他跟蹤我們？
－阿爾比，走吧
Could you please drive?
可以開車了嗎，拜託
- Please?
- Something wrong?
－怎麼了嗎？
－爸，發動，我們走了
Dad, start the car. Let's go.
What?
Can you tell me
what's going on, please?
可以告訴我是怎麼回事嗎？
- There's some guys following us.
- Who?
－有人跟蹤我們
－誰？
露西亞認識的人
Just some guys Lucia knows.
What should I do?
我該怎麼辦？
Just pull over. Stop!
停車吧‥
我來跟他談
I'll talk to him.
－（意語）你是聾了嗎？
－（意語）沒有‥
What should we do?
What do we do here?
－我們該怎麼辦？
－爸，我不知道
Dad, I don't know.
－我們走了
－不要
（意語）別煩我‥
（意語）我說別煩我
- Hey.
- What's going on here?
怎麼回事？
No.
不要
I'm going with him.
我要跟他走
不行，我們不會坐視不管
No, we're not gonna let
that happen. We can handle him.
我們有辦法對付他
你們沒辦法的
No, you can't.
Do you want us
to call the police?
要我們幫你報警嗎？
The police? No! No, no, no, no.
報警？
不行‥
聽著，我沒事
Listen, guys. I'm fine.
He's upset,
I just have to talk with him.
他不高興，我跟他談談就沒事了
We can't let you go
with him. No.
我們不能讓你跟他離開
Yeah, but we're also not
gonna escalate things further.
－不能讓情況失控
－拜託你們
Please! Don't let this
spoil your day.
別因為我壞了你們的興致
Have your reunion and...
去找你們的親戚
我們今天晚上見
see you tonight. Okay? I'm fine.
好嗎？
我沒事的
- You're sure?
- Yes.
－你確定嗎？
－確定
Okay.
- All right.
- I will call you.
－好吧
－我再打給你
- Okay.
- I'm fine.
我沒事
怎麼回事？
你們放任她被綁架嗎？
What happened?
You're gonna just
let her get abducted?
That's what she wanted, Dad.
那是她自己的意思，爸
Oh, no.
不行
Don't go with him!
別跟他走
No, that was yesterday!
＂哈珀：我回房間拿帽子＂
在嗎？
Hello?
Hold on, just one second. Hello?
－等我一下
－在嗎？
What the fuck?
搞什麼？
老天
Jesus!
－那麼沒耐性
－你幹嘛上門閂？
So impatient!
Why did you latch the door?
I didn't know I did.
我沒注意到
What? You obviously did.
什麼？
你明明就上了門閂
應該是習慣吧
Habit, I guess?
Since when is latching
the door your habit?
你什麼時候習慣上門閂了？
I had a tequila shot at the bar,
I wasn't really thinking.
我在酒吧喝了一杯龍舌蘭
腦筋不太清楚
You had a tequila shot, and then
you had to come up to get a hat?
你喝了一杯龍舌蘭
然後想到要上來拿帽子？
Yeah, I felt like
I was getting burned.
對，我覺得快要曬傷了
Let's go back down.
我們下樓吧
為什麼這扇門開著？
Why is this door open?
Is it? I don't know.
開著嗎？
我沒注意到
- I have no idea.
- Was Cameron in here?
－我不曉得
－卡麥隆剛才在這裡嗎？
- No.
- Where is he?
不在
他在哪裡？
Uh. Pr... probably in his room.
大概在房裡吧
他也要拿東西，怎麼了？
He said had
to get something, too. Why?
你們一起上來的？
So, you came up here together?
Yeah? So?
What is your deal?
對，那又怎樣？
你想說什麼？
- This door should be locked.
- Then lock it.
這扇門應該上鎖
那就上鎖啊
你們兩個
Hey, guys. Wait up.
等我
Came to get my book. Come on.
我上來拿書，走吧
Are you coming?
你要來嗎？
Now what?
現在該怎麼辦？
We came all this way.
Might as well go in.
都大老遠跑來了，還是進去吧
是啊
Yeah.
Hello, uh,
we don't, uh, speak...
你好，我們不會說‥
Non parlo Italiano.
But, uh, my name...
（意語）我們不會說意語
我叫多米尼克狄格拉索
is Dominic Di Grasso.
狄格拉索
Di Grasso.
You are Di Grasso, sì?
你也叫狄格拉索，是嗎？
（意語）對
Sì.
My mother was
from Testa dell'Acqua.
我母親來自特斯塔德阿瓜
From here.
她是這裡人
She left to go to America.
她離開這裡，去了美國
Sì.
Now, uh, we've come back
對，我們回來是想尋根
to find where we're from.
Um, we think that,
uh, we are related.
我們可能有血緣關係
你們是我們的親戚
You're our relatives.
You and I are cousins!
你們是我的親戚‥
Cousins.
Um...
（意語）我們是親戚
- Cugini!
- Cugini.
（意語）親戚
外頭是什麼聲音？
－是你母親嗎？
－對
媽媽
Huh?
這裡有三個男的
我們需要男人做什麼？
Could we say
buongiorno, uh, a tua madre?
我們可以跟你母親說聲早安嗎？
Eh.
Woah.
Grazie.
（意語）謝謝
（意語）太太
Signora.
We are your cousins
from America.
我們是你在美國的親戚
My mother was
from Testa dell'Acqua!
我母親來自特斯塔德阿瓜
她是這裡人
From here!
滾出我家，我不認識你
Huh?
No, no.
走吧，我們什麼都不知道
誰都不認識，快離開
No, no, no, no.
We come in peace!
我們沒有惡意
I think we should leave.
－快滾　－爺爺，走吧
- No, we're related. We're rel...
- Come on. Dad, Nonno, let's go.
－我們是親戚‥　－快滾
Nonno, we should go. Let's go.
－走吧
－抱歉‥
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Sorry, guys.
抱歉打擾了
（意語）走吧
Bah!
Let's get outta here.
－我們走吧　－我們還要吃午餐
不准回來
還敢來要錢，真不要臉
Let's get outta here.
－走吧　－小心我用菜薊砸你
Not quite what I imagined.
－（意語）好大的膽子
－跟我想像的不一樣
我詛咒你們
（意語）不要臉
滾吧
（意語）快走‥
他很虛偽，我跟他沒有很要好
He is a slimeball.
I didn't mean to say he's, like,
my best friend or anything.
我只是要你承認而已
I just want you
to admit it, that's all.
對，他是很有趣
但我只有這個意思
Yeah. I'd... he can
be a fun time. That's all.
That's all I meant.
You wanna try this?
It's actually kinda good.
你想喝喝看嗎？
出乎意料地好喝
你怎麼這麼開心？
Why are you in a good mood?
What?
你說什麼？
Now, all of a sudden,
you're in a good mood? Why?
你突然間開心起來了
為什麼？
Because we're in Sicily,
and it's beautiful!
因為我們人在西西里，這裡很美
還有‥
And because...
at the bar, Cameron confirmed
everything that you said.
在酒吧的時候
卡麥隆證實了你的說法
- He did?
- Yeah. Basically.
－真的嗎？
－真的
差不多啦
Hi!
－老婆
－你們‥
- What's up, honey?
- Okay, guys.
－聽了可別恨我
－怎麼了？
- Don't hate me, but, wow!
- What?
- That massage was amazing!
- Oh, really?
－按摩太棒了
－真的嗎？
－真的
－太棒了，我為你開心
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's awesome.
- I'm happy for you.
- Yeah?
－是嗎？
－對啊
- Yeah.
- Well,
而且我的按摩師超帥的
then you'll also be happy
to know that my masseur
- was so hot.
- What?
－什麼？
－是真的
- Yeah.
- No!
－不會吧
－有點像提摩西夏勒梅
Kinda looked like
Timothée Chalamet.
－不錯喔
－但他肌肉比較多
- Oh, nice!
- But he had muscles.
什麼？
提摩西夏勒梅？
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
Timothée Sham-a-lay?
Tell me
he didn't touch your boobs.
他沒摸你胸部吧
- I asked him to.
- Dirty slut!
我要他摸了
你這蕩婦
－你吃醋了嗎？
－當然
- Are you jealous?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- I want a fucking divorce!
我要離婚
小卡，夠了
- Cam! Stop it!
- Oh! You are...
你真是‥
- Just kidding.
- Mm.
Whoo! Fucking hell!
太爽了
I fucking love beer,
－我超愛啤酒的，你懂嗎？
－我懂
- know what I mean?
- Yeah, I know.
How's your thing?
－你的好喝嗎？
－好喝
- It's good, yeah.
- Yeah?
Uh, do you feel like we should
head back to the house soon?
我們是不是該回去了？
I feel like the party's probably
starting. I mean...
派對感覺要開始了
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck that, fuck that.
不行‥
Uh, let's get another one.
我們再來一輪
Geezer?
服務生
Can we get, uh, two more, yeah?
再給我們來兩杯，謝了
Nice one.
Nah, don't worry.
別擔心
My uncle's parties, they start
late and they finish late.
我叔叔的派對
很晚開始也很晚結束
So, we're good.
趕得上的
Fuck me sideways.
我的天啊
天啊，你太美了
Oh, my God.
You look stunning.
No, stunning.
真的美艷動人，轉一圈
- Turn around.
- No.
- Come on.
- No, my ass looks big.
－快
－不行，我屁股太大了
No, it d... Come on.
沒這回事‥讓我看看
你又大又美的屁股
Let's see your big,
beautiful arse
穿那件美麗淺橙色洋裝的樣子
in that amazing
symphony of salmon.
Yes!
就是這樣
- And there's more good news.
- Yeah?
－還有一個好消息
－什麼？
我為你找到了今晚完美的男伴
I found the perfect
arm candy for you tonight.
What do you mean?
什麼意思？
他是巴勒摩最性感的異性戀男子
I mean literally the sexiest
heterosexual in Palermo.
- Oh. Who is this person?
- Niccolò. Gorgeous.
－他是誰？
－尼柯羅
他不只英俊，據說下面還很雄偉
Notoriously well-hung. Not that
我沒有親眼見識過，真是可惜
I've seen it firsthand...
he said, crestfallen.
But believe me, I've tried.
相信我，我試過了
Well, what does he do
for a living?
他做什麼工作？
什麼都做一點
Oh, this and that.
Niccolò may or may not have ties
尼柯羅可能和本地
某個很有權勢的家族有關係
to a very influential
local family.
Oh, he joined the mafia?
你是指黑手黨嗎？
我提到那三個字了嗎？
我沒有提到
Did I say that?
I didn't say that.
We don't use
that word in Palermo.
在巴勒摩不能說那三個字
I know Niccolò because
he supplies all my parties
我認識尼柯羅
我的派對都仰賴他
提供最能助興的玩意兒
with the best party favors.
Yeah, but,
I'm not gonna be his type.
但是‥我不可能是他喜歡的類型
Don't be ridiculous.
別說笑了，他是你的囊中物
It's in the bag, as they say.
走吧，客人都到了
Come on. There are people here.
Here's Penelope Bianchi.
－見過潘妮洛普畢昂奇
－幸會
- Nice to meet you.
我的好友艾蜜莉費茲羅伊
My dear friend,
Emily Fitzroy. Peppe Tasca.
－佩佩泰斯卡
－幸會
What an honor.
They're lovely people,
but we could be there all night.
他們人很好
但可能得跟他們耗一整晚
Okay.
再見
Oh, Niccolò. Here he is.
尼柯羅，我們來了
就是他
Hello. Hey.
－（意語）這就是我提到的女士
－你好
你好‥
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you.
幸會‥
（意語）幸會
- Piacere.
- Mm.
Yeah. Are you S... Sicilian?
你是西西里人嗎？
- Yes. I'm from Palermo.
- Oh.
是，巴勒摩本地人
Oh. Oh, okay.
Little pick-me-up?
要提神一下嗎？
I'm, uh... I haven't done that
in a long time.
我很久沒吸了
It's like riding a bike.
吸過就不會忘記
Oh.
（意語）拜託，跟我一起吸吧
Oh. Oh.
- Let's do it.
- Uh. Okay.
一起吸吧
好吧‥
- Okay.
- Here.
來
- Do you feel it?
- I do.
－感覺到了嗎？
－感覺到了
- Yeah.
- It's very pure.
這貨很純
Yeah. And fresh, yeah.
對啊，還很新鮮
Well, this is going
rather well, isn't it?
很順利吧？
I... I love your giant pupils.
我喜歡你的大瞳孔
- Thank you.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
謝謝
We will have fun tonight.
我們今晚會玩得很愉快
- Ciao.
（意語）你好‥
你準備好就可以走了
Ah! Uh, sì. Sì. Uh...
（意語）好‥
我要先做一件事再離開
好
Okay.
我訂了一個很棒的地方
太好了
我想跟你說跟沙爾瓦多有關的事
好啊，是什麼事？
Ah! Sì.
他常常和我調情
讓我有點不舒服
天啊，我很抱歉
No, no, no.
不行‥我立刻找他談談
謝謝你
Grazie.
其實我在想
或許你能派他回海灘俱樂部
讓羅可回到櫃臺
我一定會讓沙爾瓦多回海灘
你可以放心
Okay.
但我得找其他人站櫃臺
我希望是羅可，因為‥
他是我男朋友
Ah.
－羅可嗎？
－對
他是你男朋友？
對，我們還不想告訴大家‥
我們訂婚了
恭喜你
Grazie.
（意語）謝謝
- Um...
- Uh...
所以你能讓羅可回櫃臺嗎？
我保證我們會守規矩
會保持距離
我不知道，我得想一下
我再告訴你
好
Okay. Okay. Grazie.
（意語）謝謝你
那等你忙完，我們就能出發了
老實說，我頭痛得不得了
還有很多事要做，不然先取消吧
今天是你生日，你確定嗎？
沒關係，生日跟平常沒什麼兩樣
今晚就算了，我們明天見
－好，明天見　－明天見
生日快樂
Grazie.
謝謝你
I don't know why they keep
giving us these menus.
不知道他們幹嘛還給菜單
我們都會背了
We know 'em
back to front by now.
You... you okay, man?
你還好嗎，兄弟？
Harper told me that you,
uh, said something to her.
哈珀說你告訴她了
Yeah.
對，當然
Of course. I said, uh, you know,
我說你什麼都沒做‥
you had done nothing wrong
and you've been a good boy.
你一直都很乖
Stop flirting with my wife.
I'm not a fool.
別勾引我老婆了，我不是笨蛋
All right.
好
D... Dude, are you being serious?
老兄，你是認真的嗎？
Were you in our room?
你去過我們房間嗎？
- What? When?
- Today.
什麼時候？
今天
你去過我們房間嗎？
Were you? In our room?
No. Of course not.
當然沒有
I know you got naked
in front of her.
我知道你曾經在她面前脫個精光
- What?
- On the first day...
－什麼？
－來這裡的第一天
What... what are you
talking about?
－你在說什麼？
－你跟我借泳褲的時候
When you borrowed
my bathing suit.
我知道你在打什麼主意
I know what you're doing, man.
伊森，你瘋了嗎？
E, are you... losing it?
你有沒有去我們房間？
Were you
in our fucking room, man?
Just tell me the tru...
－跟我說實話‥
－那台機器‥
Oh, well,
you have to get a studio.
你得找間工作室
Can't be consistent
with the classes, you know?
－太不穩定了，你懂嗎？
－我也有這個問題
Yeah.
I struggle with that, too.
Oh, my gosh, wow.
天啊
I actually think
little Timmy Chalamet
我的背被提摩西夏勒梅整慘了
did fuck up my back.
現在開始痛了
- It's starting to really hurt.
- Oh, sorry.
－真慘
－不會吧
No.
- Do you have any aspirin?
- Uh. I think I might.
－你有阿斯匹靈嗎？
－可能有
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
－謝謝
－不客氣
Thanks.
謝了
Watch the sun rise
On a tropic isle
Just remember, darling
All the while
你好，里卡多
可以給我一杯馬丁尼嗎？
You belong to me
＂你屬於我＂
See the marketplace
In old Algiers
＂去逛阿爾及爾的市場＂
謝謝
Grazie.
Send me photographs
And souvenirs
＂寄照片和紀念品給我＂
Just remember
When a dream appears
爸？
Dad?
You belong to me
你還好嗎？
You okay?
You always think
there's gonna be a homecoming.
我一直以為會跟回家一樣
The embrace of a woman...
會有一個女人擁抱你
who tells you
you've done all right.
告訴你，你做得很好了
Well, there is no homecoming.
這裡沒有家
Not for me, not anymore.
沒有我的家，再也沒有了
Not very hungry.
我不餓
Think I'ma just get
a drink at the lounge.
我去酒吧喝一杯就好
Fly the ocean In a silver plane
＂搭著銀色的飛機飛越海洋＂
See the jungle
When it's wet with rain
＂看看多雨的叢林＂
＂請你記得，等我回到家＂
Just remember
When I'm home again
You belong to
＂你屬於‥＂
＂我＂
Me
謝謝
Grazie.
You know,
you're really very good.
你唱得很好
Well, you're better
than the last guy.
比上一個歌手好，他唱得太爛了
- Oh.
- He was... terrible.
Grazie.
謝謝
我有一個歌迷了
Well, I have one fan.
Thank you.
謝謝
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
謝謝
I love Palermo.
我愛巴勒摩
Palermo loves you.
巴勒摩也愛你
- Ah!
- I'm... Wait.
我‥等一下
別告訴任何人有這個房間
Don't tell anyone, okay?
- About this room.
- No.
－沒有人知道
－這是我們的秘密基地
- Nobody knows.
- This is our secret place.
- Wow.
- Oh, wait a minute.
等一下
Can we look in your cocaine bag?
－可以翻你的古柯鹼袋嗎？
－可以啊
- Yeah, sure.
- 'Cause I...
－因為我還想吸
－好
- I want some more.
- Yeah.
Ooh, look.
你看
- Yeah.
- You got a gun.
你有槍耶
- Wow! You...
- And I always carry it with me.
我隨身攜帶
You got a...
What were you doing with a gun?
你帶槍要做什麼？
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
Yeah.
－沒什麼‥
－好性感
- That is so sexy.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I want it.
- You wanna start?
我要
Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh.
Huh.
我沒看過你喝酒
今天是我的生日
你一個人慶生？
No.
沒有人會幫我慶生
你應該去同志酒吧，搭訕辣妹
我告訴你一件事
一個秘密
因為我有點醉了
我從來沒跟女人做過
怎麼會？
連我都跟女人做過
Okay.
總之‥
但你喜歡女生，對嗎？
那你為什麼沒有‥
我想送你一個禮物
我來幫你
Hey.
冷靜點
Hey, hey.
我想吻你
你瘋了
Okay.
好吧
這裡不行
這個飯店有上百個房間
你一定知道哪一間是空房
二樓有一間空的套房
我們走吧
我有萬用鑰匙
真的嗎？
走了啦
天啊
What does he want from you?
他想要你做什麼？
He wants to control me.
他想控制我
He won't let me go, you know.
他不願意讓我離開
What would it take
for him to let you go?
要怎樣他才願意讓你離開？
錢，他說我欠錢
Money. He says I owe him.
I make a lot of money for him.
I told you, he is crazy.
我明明幫他賺了很多錢
我就說，他是瘋子
但這不是你的問題
But it's not your problem.
你很善良
真希望所有男人都跟你一樣
祝你生日快樂
祝你生日快樂‥
瓦倫蒂娜
祝你生日快‥
樂
Why we going?
It's too early.
你要去哪裡？
時間還早
No, it's... it's time to go.
才怪，我們該走了
I'm forever blowing bubbles
＂我總是在吹泡泡＂
Pretty bubbles
＂漂亮的泡泡‥＂
Oi!
－（意語）不看路？
－看路，王八蛋
Watch where
you're fucking going, you cunt!
Sorry. Sorry.
－抱歉‥
－（意語）你有什麼毛病
- Hey, hey. Hey.
- What's wrong with ya?
－混帳
－抱歉
Dickhead!
－（意語）滾啦
－你想去那個派對嗎？
Sorry.
- Hey. Look, look. Let's just...
- Vaffanculo...
- Let's...
- you fuckin' prick.
You wanna go to the party?
－回去參加派對吧
－什麼，不行‥
- Let's go to the party. Yeah?
- What? Oh.
No, no, no, no, no.
我們喝太醉了，不能開車
No, we can't drive.
We're too drunk.
It's all right. We'll just
get a hotel, yeah?
沒事，我們去旅館吧
我有我叔叔的信用卡
I got my uncle's credit card.
Yeah?
好嗎？
Why is it so sad? Smile.
怎麼愁眉苦臉的？
笑一個啊
Ah, it's just a bunch
of fuckin' gays and old hags.
不過是一群同性戀和老太婆
We'll make our own party, yeah?
And we'll be satisfied.
我們可以開自己的派對
你會滿足的
Finally be satisfied. Mwah!
終於能滿足
Fortune's always hiding
＂運氣總是躲著我＂
I've looked everywhere
＂我找遍了所有角落＂
＂我總是在吹泡泡＂
I'm forever blowing bubbles
Pretty bubbles in the air!
＂漂亮的泡泡飛滿天＂
西漢姆聯
United!
Hello?
在嗎？
Hold on, just one second. Hello?
－等我一下
－在嗎？
Jesus! So impatient.
老天，那麼沒耐性
I found my Ambien.
Do you want one?
我找到安眠藥了，你要嗎？
- Huh?
- Do you want an Ambien?
－什麼？
－你要安眠藥嗎？
Uh. No.
不用
- Oh.
- Away from the public, okay?
去隱密一點的地方
Yeah?
－（意語）你好美
－是嗎？
（意語）等我一下，我馬上回來
Oh. I don't speak Italian.
Thought I told you.
我跟你說過，我聽不懂意語
- Okay. I come back.
- Mm. Okay.
－我會回來
－好
- Just give me one second.
- Mm. Mm.
等我一下
Oh. Oh. Oh.
Wow.
Oh.
Wow!
Uh. I'm... I'm so nervous.
我好緊張
Just sit down.
坐下
Mm.
It's just...
你長得太帥了
You're just really handsome.
－是嗎？
－我不知道
- Yeah?
- I don't know...
（意語）你也很美
Mm.
Hey.
Oh, it's a nice room, innit?
這房間很棒吧？
Yeah. It's fine,
I guess.
還不錯，應該吧
Well, it's free.
而且不用錢
Must be nice
to have a rich uncle.
叔叔有錢還真好
Yeah, well...
這個嘛‥
he's not rich.
他其實沒什麼錢
Not really anyway. He's spent
most of it, hasn't he?
至少不是真的有錢
他花錢如流水
You've seen the way he lives.
你也看過他的生活方式
Got his boat.
他的船，他的房子
His house.
These fucking princesses,
and lords,
跟那些公主勛爵打交道
and these posh fuckers, yeah?
那些上流混蛋
They got their palazzos.
他們有宮殿
They ain't got no money.
但沒有半毛錢
He was gonna have
to sell Villa Pisano.
他本來還打算賣掉皮薩諾別墅
It's his family's fucking house!
那可是他們家族的祖產耶
你是說你們家族吧？
Your family, too, though, right?
因為他是你的叔叔，對吧？
Because he's your uncle. Right?
That would have
fucking killed him.
要是賣了，他肯定會崩潰
But he doesn't have to?
但他不必賣了？
Well, he's coming
into money now, isn't he?
他現在有錢了，不是嗎？
是這樣嗎？
Is he?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
沒錯‥
And he's gonna help his friends.
而且他會幫他朋友
'Cause he's... he's...
He's very giving.
因為他‥
非常慷慨
I'm just happy that...
That I get to, you know,
我很高興我能‥
幫到他
help him now.
'Cause he's helped me.
因為他幫過我
How are you helping him?
你怎麼幫他？
I was in a fucking hole.
我曾經淪落谷底
You know, you complain
about your life, yeah?
你剛才抱怨你過得有多苦
But really,
you should just shut it,
你沒資格說
因為你沒真正吃過苦頭
'cause you ain't never been
in a fuckin' hole like that.
Nah.
沒錯
And then he comes along and...
然後他出現了‥
沒有人是完美的
You know, no one's perfect.
Sometimes you do things
you don't wanna do.
有時你得做你不想做的事
- You know?
- No...
－你懂嗎？
－不懂
What do you mean?
What kind of hole?
你指的是什麼？
什麼谷底？
Fucking deep hole, man.
很深很深的谷底
Very fucking deep.
深不見底
待續
謝謝觀賞